DJ All I do is win win no matter what
got money on my mind I can never get it
enough and every time I step up in the
building everybody hands go
up and they stay there and they St yeah
and they stay there up down cuz all I do
is win win win and if you going in put
your
L ludicrous going in on the verse cuz I
never been defeated and I won't stop now
keep your hands up get him in the sky
for the homies that a make it in my
folks lock down I never went nowhere but
they saying lud's back blame it on that
kind je the hood call it ludak and I'm
on this foolish track so I spit my
foolish flow my hands go up and down
like strippers booties go my first to
still be serving tight like a million
virgins last time on a college remix now
I'm only your no virgin can't never
count me out y'all better Count Me In
got 20 bank account accountant Count Me
In make millions every year the South
champion cuz all I do all I all all all
I do Isn no matter what got money on my
mind I can never get it up and every
time I step up in the building everybody
hands go
up and they stay down and they say yeah
and they say there down down down cuz
all I do is
and if you put your hands in the make
down in my low head on the S you know
serving me a no no clean as a whistle as
I pull out in my RO yellow bone
passenger they see it they
say back it up my [__] call me Lo down
for AR traffic make me pull that ask you
what you laughing at represent that mud
dir it money [__] you better get your
right we come together holding Eng look
we all strapping all black it's
like you riding to what cuz we riding T
night you riding with me cuz you wasn't
riding no matter what got money on my
mind I can never get it up and every
time I step up in the building everybody
has go
up and they stay down and they stay down
and stay down down down down cuz all I
do
Isn and if you going in put your
hands heat in the Kitchen pot on the
stove water getting boil dop Snoopy in
the system over I've been running this
rap game since I was 20 years old I hung
with the worst of them bust my bur up
them up TOS them up Hard Away them up
I'm PR up bless don't mess with us we
like the you in the back to back set a
track hit the lick get it back if the
trick jump the track [__] I want my
money back time and time again while I'm
slipping on this D said it best just win
baby all I do is win no matter what got
money on my mind I can never get it up
and every time I step up in the building
everybody hands go up
and they stay down and they stay down
and they stay down down down down cuz
all I do
is and if you go in put your hands in
the air make them St
down
DJ All I do is win win win no matter
what got money on my mind I can never
get it up and every time I step up the
building everybody hands go
up and they stay there and they St yeah
and they say
there cuz all I do is s s s and if you
go in
put l ludicrous going in on the verse
cuz I never been defeated and I won't
stop now keep Your Hand